Guide to the Records of the Student Senators Council RG.44.0.1
New York University Archives
- Series V: Governance and Policy, 1976-2012; 5.25 Linear Feet in 12 manuscript boxes
  - Rules and Organization, 2006-2007 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Senate Rules of Procedure, 2006-2007 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Election of Officers, 2007-2008 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Organization and Governance (SCOG), 2007-2008 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Resolutions, 2007-2008 (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - Rules and Organization, 2007-2008 (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - Senate Rules of Procedure, 2007-2008 (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - Alcohol Policy, 2008-2009 (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - Bylaw 31: University Senate, 2008-2009 (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - Organization and Governance (SCOG), 2008-2009 (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - Protest and Dissent, Policy On, 2008-2009 (Box 97, Folder 15)
  - Resolutions, 2008-2009 (Box 97, Folder 16)
  - Rules and Organization, 2008-2009 (Box 97, Folder 17)
  - Senate Committee on Organization and Governance (SCOG), 2008-2009 (Box 97, Folder 18)
  - Senate Rules of Procedure, 2008-2009 (Box 97, Folder 19)
  - Senate Rules of Procedure and Student Council Constitution, 2010 (Box 97, Folder 20)
  - University Policies, 2011-2012 (Box 97, Folder 21)
- Series VI: Events, 1976-2009; 8.48 Linear Feet in 15 manuscript boxes and 3 shared oversize flat boxes
  Series VI contains materials pertaining to events hosted by the Student Senators Council during the academic school year. Examples of events include an End of the Year Reception, book fairs, annual dinners and banquets for the senators, the Violet Ball, as well as the All University Games. Promotional material, correspondence, administrative files, photographs, and invitations pertaining to any of these events are found within this series.
  - Awards Dinner, Trustees Dinner, 1976-1977 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Orientation Dinner, 1977 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Presidential Dinner, 1977-1978 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Student Senators Council - End of Year Reception, 1978-1979 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - End of the Year Reception, 1979-1980 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Urban Survival Conference - School of Education, Health, Nursing, and Arts Professions (SEHNAP), 1979-1980 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - End of the Year Reception, 1980-1981 (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Community Relations/Luncheon, 1981-1982 (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - End of the Year Reception, 1981-1982 (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - Fund Raising Activities, 1981-1982 (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - Theater Party, 1981-1982 (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - Disability Awareness Day, 1982-1983 (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - End of the Year Reception, 1982-1983 (Box 98, Folder 13)
  - Information Day, 1982-1983 (Box 98, Folder 14)
  - Dinners, Banquets, Honors, etc…, 1983-1984 (Box 98, Folder 15)
  - Receptions: Mid-Year and Year-End, 1984 (Box 98, Folder 16)
  - Dinners, Banquets, etc…, 1984-1985 (Box 98, Folder 17)
  - End of the Year Reception, 1984-1985 (Box 98, Folder 18)
  - Chancellor's Service Awards, 1985-1986 (Box 98, Folder 19)
  - Dinners, Banquets, etc…, 1985-1986 (Box 98, Folder 20)
  - Disability Awareness Week, 1985-1986 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Guest Attendance List, 1985-1986 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Inter-School Activities, 1985-1986 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Leadership Workshop, 1985-1986 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Avrim Pengas Agreement, 1986 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Dinners, Banquets, ets…, 1986-1987 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Chancellor's Service Awards, 1987-1988 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Dinners, Banquets, etc…, 1987-1988 (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - Year End Reception, 1987-1988 (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - Dinners, Banquets, etc…, 1988-1989 (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - Holiday Drive, 1988-1989 (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - Chancellor's Service Awards, 1989-1990 (Box 99, Folder 12)
  - Dinners, Banquets, etc…, 1989-1990 (Box 99, Folder 13)
  - Disability Awareness Week, 1989-1990 (Box 99, Folder 14)
  - Earth Day, 1989-1990 (Box 99, Folder 15)
  - Violet Ball, 1989-1990 (Box 99, Folder 16)
  - Washington Square Park, 1989-1990 (Box 99, Folder 17)
  - Book Fair, 1990-1991 (Box 99, Folder 18)
  - Dinners, Banquets, etc…, 1990-1991 (Box 99, Folder 19)
  - Violet Ball, 1990-1991 (Box 99, Folder 20)
  - Violet Ball Flyers, 1991 (Box 99, Folder 21)
  - Book Fair, 1991-1992 (Box 99, Folder 22)
  - Council Reports (All University Lip Sync Contest), 1991-1992 (Box 99, Folder 23)
  - Dinners, Banquets, etc…, 1991-1992 (Box 99, Folder 24)
  - Diversity Weekend, 1991-1992 (Box 99, Folder 25)
  - Violet Ball, 1991-1992 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Violet Ball Advertisements, 1991-1993 (Box Shared University Archives 147, Folder 8)
  - Book Fair, 1992-1993 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Dinners, Banquets, etc…, 1992-1993 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Violet Ball, 1992-1993 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Book Fair, 1993-1994 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Dinners, Banquets, etc.., 1993-1994 (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Leadership Weekend, 1993-1994 (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - Violet Ball, 1993-1994 (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - Book Fair, 1994-1995 (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - Black Student Service Center (BSSC) Black Solidarity Day 1994, 1994-1995 (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - Dinners, Banquets, etc…, 1994-1995 (Box 100, Folder 11)
  - Leadership Weekend, 1994-1995 (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - Violet Ball, 1994-1995 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Book Fair, 1995-1996 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Dinners, Banquets, etc…, 1995-1996 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Forum, 1995-1996 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Leadership Weekend, 1995-1996 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Senior Formal, 1995-1996 (Box 101, Folder 6-7)
  - Violet Ball, 1995-1996 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Book Fairs, 1996-1997 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Commencement, 1996-1997 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Dinners, Banquets, etc…, 1996-1997 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Leadership Weekend, 1996-1997 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Undergraduate Affairs, Senior Formal, 1996-1997 (Box 102, Folder 6-7)
  - Violet Ball, 1996-1997 (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Book Fair, 1997-1998 (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Dinners, Banquets, etc…, 1997-1998 (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Leadership Weekend, 1997-1998 (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Violet Ball, 1997-1998 (Box 103, Folder 5-6)
  - Violet Ball, 1998 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Book Fair, 1998-1999 (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Dinners, Banquets, etc…, 1998-1999 (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Leadership Weekend, 1998-1999 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Violet Ball, 1998-1999 (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Book Fair, 1999-2000 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Dinners, Banquets, etc…, 1999-2000 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Flier Distribution, 1999-2000 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Games, All-University, 1999-2000 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Millenium, 1999-2000 (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - NYU All-Univeristy Games - Photographs, 1999-2000 (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Violet Ball, 1999-2000 (Box 105, Folder 7-8)
  - Violet Ball Planning, 1999-2000 (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - All-University Games Poster, 2000, 2002 (Box Shared University Archives 097, Folder 5)
  - Book Fair, 2000-2001 (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - Dinners, Banquets, etc…, 2000-2001 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Games, All-University, 2000-2001 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Leadership Weekend, 2000-2001 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Violet Ball, 2000-2001 (Box 106, Folder 4, Box Shared University Archives 097, Folder 7)
  - Book Fair, 2001-2002 (Box 106, Folder 5-6)
  - Dinners, Banquets, etc…, 2001-2002 (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - Senior Week, 2001-2002 (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - University Games, 2001-2002 (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Violet Ball, 2001-2002 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Book Fair, 2002-2003 (Box 107, Folder 2-4)
  - Dinners, Banquets, etc…, 2002-2003 (Box 107, Folder 5-6)
  - Distinguished Teachers, 2002-2003 (Box Shared University Archives 145, Folder 12)
  - Lotterized Dinners - Student Roundtables, 2002-2003 (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - Senior Week, 2002-2003 (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - University Games, 2002-2003 (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - Violet Ball, 2002-2003 (Box 108, Folder 1-2)
  - Blood Drive, 2003-2004 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Book Fair, 2003-2004 (Box 108, Folder 4-5)
  - Dinners, Banquets, etc.., 2003-2004 (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Information Sent to SSC/UCSL, 2003-2004 (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Town Hall Meetings, 2003-2004 (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - University Games, 2003-2004 (Box 108, Folder 9-10)
  - Violet Ball, 2003-2006 (Box 109, Folder 1-2)
  - Violet Ball, Soap Box Forum, University Games Fliers, 2003-2004 (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Blood Drive, 2004-2005 (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Book Fair, 2004-2005 (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Dinners, Banquets, etc.., 2004-2005 (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - University Games, 2004-2005 (Box 109, Folder 7-8)
  - Violet Ball, 2004-2005 (Box 110, Folder 1-2)
  - All-University Games, 2005-2006 (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Book Fair, 2005-2006 (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - Dinners, Banquets, etc…, 2005-2006 (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - Presidential Service Awards, 2005-2006 (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - Violet Ball, 2005-2006 (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - All-University Games, 2006-2007 (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - Dinners, Banquets, etc.., 2006-2007 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Violet Ball, 2006-2007 (Box 111, Folder 2-3)
  - Dinners, Banquets, etc.., 2007-2008 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Events Materials, 2007-2009 (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - Photocopies of Photos, 2007-2009 (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - UCSL Events, 2007-2009 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Violet Ball, 2007-2009 (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Whalen's (Book Fair), 2007-2009 (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - All-University Games, 2008 (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - Violet Ball, 2008 (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Year End Dinner, 2008 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - All University Games, 2008-2009 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Dinners, Banquets, etc.., 2008-2009 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Student Activities: Events, 2008-2009 (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Violet Ball, 2008-2009 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - All University Games, 2009 (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Violet Ball, 2009 (Box 112, Folder 8)
- Series VII: Finance, 1978-2014; 3.06 Linear Feet in 7 manuscript boxes
  Series VII contains material specifically related to the finances of the Student Senators Council. Some general financial aid information can also be found within this series since, as the representative body for the students, the SSC is involved in financial aid discussions with the administration.
  - Swift Report: Financial Exigency, 1978-1979 (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - Fund Allocation to Student Council, 1979-1980 (Box 112, Folder 10)
  - State Aid to Independent Colleges, 1979-1980 (Box 112, Folder 11)
  - Tuition Costs, 1979-1980 (Box 112, Folder 12)
  - Financial Affairs - Budget, 1980-1981 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Financial Exigency, 1980-1981 (Box 112, Folder 13)
  - All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC) - Spring Budgets and Appeals, 1981-1982 (Box 113, Folder 1-3)
  - Financial Exigency, 1981-1982 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Funding: Clubs & Councils, 1981-1982 (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Press Conference: Government Aid, 1981-1982 (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - Student Activities Fee, 1981-1982 (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - 1982-1983 Budget Worksheets (Box 113, Folder 9)
  - Funding - Clubs & Councils, 1982-1983 (Box 113, Folder 10)
  - Fund Raising Campaign $1 Million, 1982-1983 (Box 113, Folder 11)
  - Student Financial Aid & Compensation, 1982-1983 (Box 113, Folder 12)
  - Financial Aid, 1983-1984 (Box 113, Folder 13)
  - Tuition Assistance Program, 1983-1984 (Box 113, Folder 14)
  - Contingency Requests, 1984-1985 (Box 114, Folder 1-2)
  - Student Activities Fund Proposal, 1984-1985 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Student Financial Aid & Compensation, 1985 (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Contingency Fund, 1986-1987 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Student Financial Aid, 1986-1987 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Council Contingency Funds (CCF) Funding, 1987-1988 (Box 114, Folder 7-8)
  - School of Continuing Education (SCE) Student Council(s) Funding, 1987-1988 (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Student Councils Members & Budgets, 1988-1989 (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - Student Financial Aid & Compensation, 1988-1989 (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - Financial Aid Peer Counselors, 1989-1990 (Box 114, Folder 12)
  - Student Affairs ECRs, 1989-1990 (Box 114, Folder 13)
  - Student Financial Aid and Compensation, 1989-1990 (Box 114, Folder 14)
  - Student Financial Aid and Compensation, 1990-1991 (Box 114, Folder 15)
  - Student Financial Aid and Compensation, 1991-1992 (Box 114, Folder 16)
  - Universit Budget, 1991-2008 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Emergency Loan Funds, 1992-1993 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Financial Affairs, 1992-1993 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Student Financial Aid and Compensation, 1992-1995 (Box 115, Folder 4-6)
  - Financial Aid Office Advisory Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Student Financial Aid and Compensation, 1995-1998 (Box 115, Folder 8-10)
  - Petty Cash Slips, 2000 (Box 115, Folder 11)
  - University Budget, 2000-2001 (Box 115, Folder 12)
  - Past SSC/UCSL Recommendations to Senate Financial Affairs Committee (SFAC), 2003 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Budget Information, 2003-2004 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Student Financial Aid and Compensation, 2003-2004 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Past SSC/USCL Recommendations to Senate Financial Affairs Committee (SFAC), 2004-2008 (Box 116, Folder 4-7)
  - Past Recommendations to Senate Financial Affairs Committee (SFAC), 2007-2008 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Student Financial Aid and Compensation, 2007-2008 (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Past Recommendations to Senate Financial Affairs Committee (SFAC), 2008 (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Budget Overview, 2008-2009 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Financial Aid & Compensation, 2008-2009 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Student Financial Aid and Compensation, 2008-2009 (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - NYU Fiscal 2010 Budget & Financial Plan - Re-engineering Advisory Committee, 2009 (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC) Budget Applications, 2009-2012 (Box 117, Folder 8-9, Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Emails about Club Budgets, 2011-2012 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Budget, 2012 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - New York University Student Council Budget Manual, 2012-2013 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Conference Funding, 2013-2014 (Box 118, Folder 5)
- Series VIII: Membership, 1975-2018; 15.75 Linear Feet in 36 manuscript boxes
  In order to become a member of the Student Senator's Councils, students from NYU's various campuses were expected to apply for a position within the SSC, submitting applications, resumes, personal statements, and in some cases, references. Although the SSC received numerous applications, only twenty-three senators are elected by the student body and twelve alternate student senators are appointed by the senators. Series VIII contains materials relating to the members of the Student Senators Council such as completed applications, election materials, advertisements, lists of Student Senators-at-Large and their alternates, committee preference sheets, and guidelines for selecting members.
  This series contains materials protected under the Federal Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA) and is permanently restricted.
  - General Life, 1975-1976 (Box 118, Folder 6-7)
  - Censure (RESTRICTED), 1977 (Box 159, Folder 6)
  - Personnel Information, 1977-1978 (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - Senators-at-Large, 1977-1978 (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Personnel Information, 1978-1979 (Box 119, Folder 3-4)
  - Attendance, 1979-1980 (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - Membership Lists, 1979-1980 (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - Senators-at-Large Ads for 80-81, 1979-1980 (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - University Disciplinary Panel, 1979-1980 (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Attendance Lists, 1980-1981 (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Censure of Members (RESTRICTED), 1980-1981 (Box 159, Folder 7)
  - Committee Assignments, 1980-1981 (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Membership (SSC), 1980-1981 (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Membership Lists, 1980-1981 (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Senators-at-Large, 1980-1981 (Box 120, Folder 6-7)
  - Alternate Senators-at-Large, 1981-1982 (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - Attendance Lists, 1981-1982 (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - Committee Preference Sheets, 1981-1982 (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Membership List/Committee Assignment, 1981-1982 (Box 120, Folder 11)
  - Senators-at-Large, 1981-1982 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Alternate Senators-at-Large, 1982-1983 (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Alternate Student Senators, 1982-1983 (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Committee Availbility Forms, UCSL, 1982-1983 (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Committee Preference Sheets, 1982-1983 (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - Guest List: Attendance at UCSL, 1982-1983 (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - Membership List/Committee Assignment, 1982-1983 (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - Personnel Information, 1982-1983 (Box 121, Folder 8)
  - Senators-at-Large, 1982-1983 (Box 121, Folder 9)
  - Senators-at-Large Applications, 1982-1983 (Box 121, Folder 10)
  - Vice Presidents & Administrators, 1982-1983 (Box 121, Folder 11)
  - Censure, 1983 (Box 159, Folder 10)
  - Alternate Senators, 1983-1984 (Box 121, Folder 14)
  - Attendance Lists, 1983-1984 (Box 121, Folder 12-13)
  - Committee Availbility Forms, 1983-1984 (Box 121, Folder 15)
  - Guest Attendance Sheets, 1983-1984 (Box 121, Folder 16)
  - Membership Lists, 1983-1984 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Personnel Information, 1983-1984 (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Senate Membership List, 1983-1984 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Student Senators-at-Large, 1983-1984 (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Student Senators-at-Large 84-85, 1983-1984 (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - Summer '83 Personnel Info, 1983-1984 (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - Attendance Lists, 1984-1985 (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - Committee Assignments, 1984-1985 (Box 122, Folder 8)
  - Committee Availability Forms, 1984-1985 (Box 122, Folder 9)
  - Guest Attendance Lists, 1984-1985 (Box 122, Folder 10)
  - Membership: 5 Years (SSC), 1984-1985 (Box 122, Folder 11)
  - Membership Information & Lists, 1984-1985 (Box 122, Folder 12)
  - SSC Committee Preference Forms, 1984-1985 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - SSC Membership Packet, 1984-1985 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Senators-at-Large for 1985-1986, 1984-1985 (Box 123, Folder 3-5)
  - Senators-at-Large Applicants, 1984-1985 (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - Student Directory, 1984-1985 (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - Student Senators-at-Large (SSC), 1984-1985 (Box 123, Folder 8, Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Summer 84 Personnel Info, 1984-1985 (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - UCSL Committee Preference Forms, 1984-1985 (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - Attendance Lists, 1985-1986 (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - Certificates of Service, 1985-1986 (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - Committee Assignments (SSC & UCSL), 1985-1986 (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - Committee Availability Forms, 1985-1986 (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - Committee Availability Forms (non-members only), 1985-1986 (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - Committee Preference Forms (non-members only), 1985-1986 (Box 124, Folder 9)
  - Committee Preference Forms: SSC, 1985-1986 (Box 124, Folder 10)
  - Committee Preference Forms: UCSL, 1985-1986 (Box 124, Folder 11)
  - Membership Information & Lists, 1985-1986 (Box 124, Folder 12)
  - Senators-at-Large Applications 86-87, 1985-1986 (Box 124, Folder 13, Box 125, Folder 1-3)
  - Attendance Lists, 1986-1987 (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - Certificates of Service, 1986-1987 (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - Committee Availability Sheets, 1986-1987 (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - Committee Preference Forms, 1986-1987 (Box 125, Folder 7)
  - Guest Attendance Lists, 1986-1987 (Box 125, Folder 8)
  - Membership Lists & Information, 1986-1987 (Box 125, Folder 9-10)
  - Senators-at-Large for 87-88, 1986-1987 (Box 126, Folder 1-2)
  - Senators-at-Large Current, 1986-1987 (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - Student Senators Council, 1986-1987 (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - Senators-at-Large Decline Letters, 1987 (Box 127, Folder 6)
  - Attendance Lists, 1987-1988 (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - Committee Availability Forms, 1987-1988 (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - Committee Preference Forms, 1987-1988 (Box 126, Folder 7)
  - Guest Attendance Lists, 1987-1988 (Box 126, Folder 8)
  - Membership Lists, 1987, 1991-1996 (Box 126, Folder 9)
  - Membership Lists/Personnel Information, 1987-1988 (Box 126, Folder 10, Box 127, Folder 1)
  - School Student Council Presidents, 1987-1988 (Box 127, Folder 2)
  - Senators-at-Large for 1988-1989, 1987-1988 (Box 127, Folder 3-4)
  - Senators-at-Large Current, 1987-1988 (Box 127, Folder 5)
  - Attendance Lists, 1988-1989 (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - Committee Availability Forms, 1988-1989 (Box 127, Folder 8)
  - Committee Preference Forms SSC & UCSL, 1988-1989 (Box 127, Folder 9)
  - Guest Attendance Lists, 1988-1989 (Box 127, Folder 10)
  - Membership Lists & Information, 1988-1989 (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - Senators-at-Large, 1989-1990, 1988-1989 (Box 128, Folder 2-3)
  - Senators-at-Large Current, 1988-1989 (Box 128, Folder 4)
  - Student Senators-at-Large Application, 1988-1989 (Box 128, Folder 5)
  - Alternate Senators, 1989-1990 (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - Attendance Lists, 1989-1990 (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - Availability Forms SSC, UCSL, non-members, 1989-1990 (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - Committee Preference Forms (SSC/UCSL/non members), 1989-1990 (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - Guest Attendance Lists, 1989-1990 (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - Membership Lists & Information, 1989-1990 (Box 129, Folder 6)
  - Senators-at-Large, 1989-1990 (Box 129, Folder 7)
  - Senators-at-Large for 1990-1991, 1989-1990 (Box 129, Folder 8-9)
  - Senators-at-Large Applications, 1989-1990 (Box 129, Folder 10)
  - Senators-at-Large Current, 1989-1990 (Box 130, Folder 1)
  - Student Senators Council Membership, 1990 (Box 130, Folder 2)
  - Attendance Lists, 1990-1991 (Box 130, Folder 3)
  - Availability Forms SSC; UCSL; members, 1990-1991 (Box 130, Folder 4)
  - Committee Preference Forms, SSC/UCSL, non members, 1990-1991 (Box 130, Folder 5)
  - Guest Attendance Lists, 1990-1991 (Box 130, Folder 6)
  - Membership Lists & Information, 1990-1991 (Box 130, Folder 7-8)
  - Senators-at-Large for A/Y 1991-1992, 1990-1991 (Box 130, Folder 9)
  - Senators-at-Large Current, 1990-1991 (Box 130, Folder 10)
  - Attendance Lists, 1991-1992 (Box 130, Folder 11)
  - Availability Forms SSC; UCSL; members, 1991-1992 (Box 130, Folder 12)
  - Awards, 1991-1992 (Box 130, Folder 13)
  - Committee Preference Forms, 1991-1992 (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - Guest Attendance Lists, 1991-1992 (Box 131, Folder 2)
  - Labels for Senators and Alternates, 1991-1992 (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - Senators-at-Large Applications, 1991-1992 (Box 131, Folder 4-5)
  - Student Senators-at-Large for 92-93, 1991-1992 (Box 131, Folder 6)
  - Student Senators-at-Large Current, 1991-1992 (Box 131, Folder 7)
  - Student Senators Membership, 1991-1992 (Box 131, Folder 8)
  - Attendance Lists, 1992-1993 (Box 131, Folder 9)
  - Committee Preference Forms, 1992-1993 (Box 131, Folder 10)
  - Guest Attendance List, 1992-1993 (Box 131, Folder 11)
  - Membership Lists and Information, 1992-1993 (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - Senators-at-Large, 1992-1993 (Box 132, Folder 3-4)
  - Student Senators-at-Large for 93-94, 1992-1993 (Box 132, Folder 5)
  - Student Senators-at-Large Current, 1992-1993 (Box 132, Folder 6)
  - At Large Applications, 1993-1994 (Box 132, Folder 7)
  - Attendance Lists, 1993-1994 (Box 132, Folder 8)
  - Committee Preference Forms (C), 1993-1994 (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - Committee Preference Forms (O), 1993-1994 (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - Guest Attendance Lists, 1993-1994 (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - Membership Lists, 1993-1994 (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - Student Senators-at-Large for 94-95, 1993-1994 (Box 133, Folder 5-6)
  - Student Senators-at-Large Current, 1993-1994 (Box 133, Folder 7)
  - Alternate Senators-at-Large, 1994-1995 (Box 133, Folder 8)
  - Attendance Lists, 1994-1995 (Box 133, Folder 9)
  - Availability Forms, 1994-1995 (Box 133, Folder 10)
  - Committee Preference Forms, 1994-1995 (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - Flier Distribution List, 1994-1995 (Box 134, Folder 2)
  - Guest Attendance Lists, 1994-1995 (Box 134, Folder 3)
  - Membership Lists, 1994-1995 (Box 134, Folder 4)
  - Student Senators-at-Large: 95-96, 1994-1995 (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - Student Senators-at-Large: Current, 1994-1995 (Box 134, Folder 6)
  - Attendance Lists, 1995-1996 (Box 134, Folder 7)